[insects chirping]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[vehicle approaching]
Okay. Manuel. right?
This is for you.
It's 25 for the vehicle
and 30 for the transport of the livestock.
Just put down "one horse"
and your signature right there.
You just said. "one horse"?
Yeah. it's only one. right?
No. it's an elephant.
You mean "really big horse?"
No. I mean an elephant.
- Look. sir…
- [trumpeting]
…the call said one…
Whoa.
What the fuck is that?
[elephant trumpeting]
Holy shit!
- Is that a fucking elephant?
- Señor. señor. señor.
Probablemente. it was some kind
of bad communication.
Bad communication? This is a truck
for fucking horses. man!
- What do I look like? A goddamn maharaja?
- All right.
And you're invited to the party.
[elephant trumpeting]
[elephant sniffs. snorts]
[cows mooing]
[ropes creaking]
[speaking Spanish]
[in English] More gas!
Come on. Come on!
Give me...
[speaking Spanish]
[engines revving]
Fuck! Fuck!
[elephant trumpets wildly]
[screaming]
[in Spanish] What the fuck are you doing?
[speaking Spanish]
God damn it!
[elephant bellowing]
[groans] Motherfucker!
[elephant trumpeting]
[speaking Spanish]
- [groans]
- [Manny shouting indistinctly]
[elephant trumpeting]
- [elephant bellowing]
- [horn honking]
- [birds chirping]
- [engines rumbling]
[elephant groaning]
[speaking Spanish]
[in English] Good evening. Officer.
What exactly is going on here?
Well. we're... I work for Don Wallach.
and we're transporting the entertainment
for a party at his house.
[elephant trumpets]
That's an elephant.
- Yes. sir.
- You got a permit?
I didn't know we needed one.
Can't drive an elephant without a permit.
Could you make an exception?
How's the guest list looking for tonight?
It's impressive.
What kind of stars are we talking about?
- Someone said Garbo. I think.
- Oh. yeah?
Yeah. I mean. that's what I heard.
So. we're talking an elephant. plus Garbo.
plus others tonight
at Don Wallach's house.
- is that right?
- That's right.
Sounds like the best party in town.
My cousin Benny lives in Reseda
with his wife and kids.
I'll see if they're free.
Who the fuck are all these people?
[in Spanish] Don't ask.
- [upbeat jazz music playing]
- ♪ One. two. three. hey ♪
[man laughing]
Does Piggy like that?
It tickles.
Playtime with potty time!
José! José!
Can you ask Wallach to give us
more King Bubbly. por favor?
Okay. [laughing]
Seriously?
[music continues]
[dishes smashing]
Would you mind showing me
to the upstairs powder room. my dear boy?
Sure. It's here down the hall.
No! No. no. upstairs.
The stairs are very steep. I think...
I can be carried.
Evening. madame. Lovely to see you.
I have to steal him. I'm afraid.
- What did you say to Elinor?
- Who?
Elinor St. John. Never speak to her.
If she ever talks to you again.
pretend like you don't understand English.
- The chicken stole my fucking coke!
- [chicken clucking]
Go fucking get it! Get it!
Give it to me!
So. upstairs is where Don keeps
his underage girls. then?
[in Spanish] I don't speak English!
- [music ends abruptly]
- [grunting]
Well. that came out of fucking nowhere.
You'll have to pay for that. ma'am.
Oh. okay.
- Uh. who are you?
- I'm security.
You're kind of shitty at your job.
You have statues coming out of nowhere.
everywhere you fucking turn.
You're very lucky I don't report you.
Where do you think you're going. ma'am?
I'm going inside.
I'm Nellie LaRoy. dummy.
There's no "Nellie LaRoy" on the list.
Okay. well. I think... Come here.
I think what's happened is my assistant
has put me under my stage name.
- Billie Dove.
- You're not Billie Dove.
Okay. what the fuck is your prob...
What is your name?
- What is your precinct?
- I'm a security guard.
- We don't have precincts. ma'am.
- You're about to not have a job. fucko!
Listen. I know you wish
you were Billie Dove...
I think you wish you were
eating my asshole...
[in English] Nellie LaRoy?
They're waiting for you.
[gentle music playing]
I'm Manuel.
I heard ya.
Oh. I didn't need your help.
- Oh. no?
- Nope.
- Billie Dove?
- Why not?
She's kind of a big star.
Well. in 30 years
she won't be a big star anymore
and she can tell her grandkids
Nellie LaRoy once used her name.
Besides. I'm already a star.
- You are?
- Yeah.
- What have you been in?
- Nothing yet.
- Who's your contract with?
- Don't have one.
Okay. I think you want to become a star.
Honey. you don't become a star.
You either are one or you ain't.
I am.
Oh. great.
Do you know where I can find some drugs?
[upbeat music playing]
We're supposed to just keep playing?
That's the idea.
It's gonna come through the front
and just kind of stomp around.
- Are you serious?
- Just stay out of its way.
Now. you know I can't afford
to get injured. Joe.
- Will you shut the fuck up?
- What?
- You heard me. you whiny bitch.
- Excuse me?
- Come on. you guys.
- You see how he just talks to me?
I talk to you like this
because every time we play in these.
you playing fucking flat.
If that elephant drop
its elephant ass on your face.
maybe you'd be home long enough
to fucking practice.
I practice nine hours a day. you fuck.
Yeah. yeah.
but I mean on saxophone. not cocksucking.
[crowd screams. cheers]
I don't have fucking time for this!
[Orville] Wake up. wake up. wake up!
What a goddamn mess.
We were just having fun! [sobs]
- [Bob] Tell it to Wallach.
- Wake up. wake up.
- [Jimmy] Where's the Mexican?
- Wake up. wake up!
Morphine. opium. ether. heroin. coke.
And Louis XIV sat on that.
[Ina] I won't pretend that everything's
fine inside when all I feel is this void.
- And all I do is I give and I give!
- [guard] Pedro!
And you. I don't even know.
where are you? Where are you?
[speaking Italian]
Stop speaking fucking Italian!
No. No. it's not.
I'm trying to have
a serious conversation with you.
Do you understand?
Our marriage is in trouble. I am unhappy!
Stop it! You are not fucking Italian!
You are from fucking Shawnee.
you goddamn fraud!
[speaking Italian]
Say one more word.
Say one more word in Italian.
and I will divorce you.
- One more.
- [in English] Okay. Okay.
[speaking Italian]
Get the fuck out!
Get the fuck out of the car! Go!
- Hey. hey.
- Get out! Go!
[speaking Italian]
I want a divorce.
[upbeat music concludes]
[speaking Italian]
- [in English] Morning. Dale.
- Evening. Mr. Conrad.
Evening.
[upbeat music playing]
- Jack! Jack!
- [man] Oh. my God! J.C.!
- Nathalie!
- It's been forever!
- Yeah.
- [Elinor] I've been saying it
since Wally Reid.
- Who needs royalty anymore?
- Madame.
- Dearest Jacky boy. we need to talk!
- I have a good story for you.
- I have your face tattooed on my back.
- Well. look at that.
Jack. for fuck's sake.
I've been trying you all week.
Will you just fucking call me back?
- [speaking Italian]
- Ciao. bella!
Come here. you moola-minting.
money machine motherfucker!
I love you!
- [Charlie] Jack. is it okay I grab this?
- Hey. Charlie. How's the missus?
- [Charlie] I think she left me.
- Hey. Mr. Conrad.
Hey. me too! Congrats!
Are you okay with March 17th
for the premiere?
No. 18th. Thursdays are always classier.
Hey. send Charlie a bottle of bourbon
and get ahold of his negative
- and make sure I don't look too shiny.
- [publicist] Yes. Mr. Conrad.
No Mrs. Conrad tonight?
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
I'm sorry. [chuckles]
I think we have a problem.
- We do?
- Yep.
This table only has one bottle.
and we're gonna need eight.
We're also gonna need two gin rickeys.
an orange blossom with brandy.
three French 75s.
Can you do a Corpse Reviver?
Gin. lemon. triple sec.
and Kina Lillet with a dash of absinthe.
- Two of those.
- [server] Two of those.
Okay. Two gin rickeys. three French...
You didn't have to do that.
you know. to get my attention.
I am so sorry. Mr. Conrad.
- I want...
- What's your name?
Jen. I just wanted you to look my way.
Jen. I'd always look your way.
[driver] Sir. George won't
come out of the car.
He's insisting I drive him
off the nearest cliff.
Right.
Be right back.
[upbeat music concludes]
[Jack] She said no. huh?
After all we've been through.
[Jack] Well. to be fair. George.
you did just meet her a week ago.
What we had was special. goddamn it.
[Jack] I know. buddy. but you're not gonna
kill yourself over it.
Save the ring and come on inside.
There's a girl asking after ya.
Yeah?
That's right.
- [glass smashing]
- [crowd clamoring from mansion]
There you go. buddy.
- Who's the girl?
- A goddess.
[sniffs. coughs]
No Paris for me.
- I'm good.
- What?
You've never done cocaine?
Of course I've done cocaine.
Well?
I do cocaine all the time. I just…
Don't make me do it alone.
- Okay. I'll do a little. Whatever.
- [chuckles]
I don't care.
I don't know. maybe Niagara Falls.
You know. "Roy." actually.
in French. means "king."
And I added the "La."
so it's "Nellie the King."
- I made that up.
- [grunts]
What about you? Where would you go?
Sorry? [sniffs]
If you could go
anywhere in the whole world.
where would you go?
[Manny sniffs]
Anywhere.
I don't know.
I always wanted to go on a movie set.
- Yeah?
- [Manny] Yeah. A movie set.
Tell me why.
- Why?
- Yeah. tell me why.
All right. um…
- I don't know why.
- [Nellie] I wanna go on a movie set too.
Why? I just want to be part
of something bigger. I guess.
Bigger than what?
Bigger than this.
I don't know. Bigger than my life.
Bigger than scooping elephant shit.
Bigger. Better. Important.
Something important.
To be part of something important.
Something that lasts.
that means something.
I love that answer.
- Yeah. making movies.
- [Nellie] I want to go on a movie set too.
Or at least I want to be there.
work there.
- learn there. I don't know.
- [Nellie] Yeah! Yeah.
I just love watching movies. you know?
- [Nellie] I love watching movies too.
- You sit there.
- And you're watching the movie and...
- And you escape.
You don't have to be
in your own shitty fucking life.
- Exactly! Exactly!
- You can be in their life.
- Or wherever!
- [Nellie] Or wherever!
You can be in the fucking Wild West!
You can be in fucking space!
- You can be like a gangster.
- Yeah!
[Manny] And people dance in movies
and people die in movies.
And they're not really dead.
It's fucking amazing.
They're not really dead.
Like literally. kill me.
[imitates gun firing]
And nothing happened. for real.
but at the same time.
it's something
even more important than life.
You can feel it.
Like... I don't know.
Movies are sad sometimes.
- Movies are fucking happy.
- They make you feel something.
- Yeah.
- One day. you and me.
we're gonna be on a movie set.
- We can have lunch together.
- Yeah. for sure.
- I don't know what I'm going to do yet.
- It'll be just you and me.
- Yeah. you and me.
- Yeah.
You know. you're not bad looking.
Thank you.
- [drum rolling]
- And now. the Rose Petal
of the Rising Sun.
Miss Lady Fay Zhu!
- [crowd cheering]
- [drum rolling concludes]
[cheering dies down. catcalls]
♪ There's one pet I like to pet ♪
[jazz music playing]
♪ Every evening we get set ♪
♪ I stroke it every chance I get ♪
♪ It's my girl's ♪
♪ Pussy ♪
[crowd cheering. whistling]
♪ Seldom plays and never purrs ♪
♪ And I love the thoughts it stirs ♪
♪ But I don't mind because it's hers ♪
♪ It's my girl's pussy ♪
[Lady Fay whistles]
♪ 'Cause I'll do anything
For my sweet pet ♪
♪ She works me to a sweat ♪
♪ And that's hard to do ♪
♪ I must first remove my gloves ♪
♪ When stroking my girl's ♪
- ♪ Pussy ♪
- [song concludes]
[crowd cheers. whistles]
[upbeat jazz music playing]
[Jack] Lady Fay. Lady Fay. come stai?
Fine. Didn't get the part.
but writing the titles on it.
I'm stuck doing
another costume picture.
and my wife's divorcing me.
Want to trade?
No.
[Jack] That woman is something.
you know?
She was completely honest with me.
Your wife?
God. no. My…
Jen. The…
Listen. I need a favor.
You know my old friend
George over there?
I wonder if you'd go talk to him.
You know.
tell him you were asking after him.
That sad man over there?
Yeah.
Listen. I'm not asking you
to fuck him.
Just. you know. make him…
feel special.
Okay.
[speaking Cantonese]
- Don't speak Cantonese to me.
- [Jack. in English] All right.
Oh. I love this song!
[upbeat jazz music playing]
[crowd cheering over music]
You! I've been looking all over for you.
We got a serious fucking situation.
- [music ends abruptly]
- There's no exit
except down the main staircase.
- Nothing in the back?
- No.
You gotta go through the ballroom.
Everyone will see her.
- Is there a doctor?
- No.
They're all high down there.
Maybe they won't care.
- If we take her out now...
- Somebody will care!
She's a fucking kid.
and she looks like she's dead.
We use the elephant.
We bring him through the front.
Everyone will look at him.
No one will look at her.
It's only 2:00.
Don wanted to save the elephant.
Fine. Get the wrangler.
Jimmy. you carry the girl with me.
Then you drive her to the hospital.
[Jimmy] Doubt she'll be able
to work tomorrow.
That's her fucking problem.
No. She's in the bar scene in Maid's Off.
Yeah. Jane Thornton. that's her.
Bar shoots tomorrow. doesn't it?
Yes.
Who the fuck invited her?
I did.
You blimp motherfucker.
- piece of fat fucking shit!
- It was her first film.
- She wanted to celebrate.
- I'll fucking... You doughboy!
You fuckhead motherfucking Humpty Dumpty!
- [Jimmy] Bob. come on! Bob!
- I'm gonna cut you up!
- [Orville] No. Bob! Don't leave me!
- [Bob] Fuck!
[upbeat music playing]
Her.
Whoever she is. we go with her tomorrow.
[man] What the fuck?
Come on! Come on. baby!
[woman screams]
Right here! I'm right here!
[upbeat music concludes]
[slow instrumental music playing]
[glass clinks]
Yeah. All right. Kapitän.
Just one more drink for old time's sake.
Sir?
I just want to say thank you for the work.
And I was wondering if perhaps. next time.
you or Mr. Wallach
might have something for me on a set?
I'll do anything.
I can paint. I can cook.
I can clean. I can do coffee...
You're where you belong.
Okay. Thank you.
[Nellie] Oh. I'm gonna raise you.
[Jimmy] You need to be on set in
three hours. You'd better get some sleep.
[laughs]
- Gentlemen.
- [man] You have a good night. Nellie.
Congratulations.
Manny!
Ain't life grand? [laughing]
[gentle music playing]
[screeches happily]
Oh. if they could see me now!
All the cunts in Lafayette called me
the ugliest mutt in the neighborhood.
Well. let them see me now!
Can you believe this. Manny?
Hey. Josie! Hey. Nana!
Why don't you kiss
my royal Angeleno hooch?
Nellie.
[in Spanish] I think I'm in love with you.
Night-night. honey.
Don't worry about that.
The car is not mine.
Chico. Hey. Chico!
Jack Conrad's passed out.
Use one of Wallach's cars
to take him home.
[gentle music concludes]
- Señor?
- [groans]
[in English] Sir? Do you have keys?
Yeah. I have keys.
[speaking Spanish]
[laughing]
Musica. Musica?
Sì. Sì.
[Italian opera music playing]
[in English] Imagine me at the opera?
That would've made Ina's folks happy.
Well. if you'll excuse me…
- [Jack singing in Italian]
- [urinating]
[in English] See my point? Come on.
[continues singing in Italian]
[in English] Ina's mom always said.
"I don't see how you can marry
someone who paints his face."
You know what we gotta do?
We gotta redefine the form.
The man who puts gasoline
in your tank
goes to the movies why?
Why? Why?
Because he feels less alone there.
Don't we owe him more
than the same old shit?
You got the guys in Europe
with the twelve-tone.
You got Bauhaus architecture.
Fucking Bauhaus. you know?
And we're still doing
costume pictures?
It's the dinosaurs. kid.
It's the ones who go to Beverly Hills
for meatballs and mint juleps
to reminisce about the old days.
when they can't see
there's so much more to be done!
We've got to innovate.
We've got to inspire.
We got to dream beyond
these pesky shells of flesh and bone.
Map those dreams onto celluloid
and print them into history.
Turn today into tomorrow
so that tomorrow's lonely man
may look up at that flickering screen
and say for the very first time.
"Eureka! I am not alone!"
Yeah.
- [screaming]
- [objects smashing]
And I'm going to bed.
[opera music playing]
[Jack] Hey. where'd you go?
You need something?
Yeah. I like you.
I want you to take me to set today.
I want you by my side.
You okay with that?
Sí.
[Jack] You ever been
on a movie set before?
[in English] No.
[Jack] You'll see.
It's the most magical place in the world.
- [in Spanish] I've heard.
- [opera music concludes]
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music concludes]
[gasps]
[soft jazz music playing]
[in Mandarin] Liu. We could use your help.
[Lady Fay. in Mandarin]
Okay. I'll be right there.
Dad got last week's check?
Yes. It was more this time. Thank you.
[in English] Hole in shirt before.
No. hole not in shirt before.
you fucking coolie!
I don't want a fucking discount! I...
Are you…
[in English] I am.
[Jack] Morning!
Time to go make a movie.
[music concludes]
[loud chatter]
- [man 1] Maid's Off?
- [Nellie] Yeah.
[man 1] Come with me.
[man 2] Higher! More!
[man 3] Now go over. put it in the pot.
Scream like a big. fat pig.
All right. All right. all right! Yes!
More whiskey! More whiskey!
Well. don't just fucking stand there!
Get the fuck out of the shot!
Peanuts! Good for hangovers!
You. You're new? You're new here?
Your first bag is free.
One bag or two? One.
And you're paying this time? Thank you.
Hurry the fuck up!
[woman] Can you stop drinking?
We are not shooting yet!
Put down the fucking glasses!
Who the fuck is this?
I asked for the girl with the tits.
This is who they found.
What happened to the tits part?
She OD'd.
[groans]
Just go. Just go. Get her made up.
- Max!
- [Max] Yes.
Just shoot the men or something.
- No tits?
- [Ruth] No tits.
All right. no tits. everybody!
We're shooting the men.
[Otto] Deise Scheißen fucks!
They are ruining my movie!
I want them on camera in five minutes!
Otto. please. please. Jack's arriving.
What about pancakes? Do you heat the syrup
or do you let the pancake do the warming?
- Heat the syrup?
- I agree!
That there is George Munn.
the best producer in the biz
and my oldest pal.
Set patrol over there is Jim Kidd.
legend of the Wild West
who made his name killing Apaches.
- Lives in Brentwood now.
- [Otto] This is bullshit!
Georgie. what's up
Von Cheeseburger's ass today?
The extras want to renegotiate their pay.
[Otto] …you motherfucker!
I do not care if the extras are revolting!
Well. put the kid on it.
The kid?
Yeah. the kid. The Mexican I brought.
He's great. What's your name?
- Me? Manuel.
- [Otto] Bullshit!
Right. Manuel. Manuel's great!
Put Manuel on it.
You have experience with strikes?
Yes.
Okay. good.
Well. these are all junkies from Skid Row.
- so they're pretty violent.
- [Otto] …you fucking assholes!
Who are you?
That's the cocksucker
they sent to screw us!
Gentlemen. I believe
you all agreed to a day's work.
And I believe I agreed
to ram this knife up the asshole
of the first faggot they sent over!
[crowd cheers menacingly]
This is where you kiss the apparition. ja?
Ja.
She has led you to your destiny
through fate.
through your lifetime to this moment. ja?
- Mm-hmm.
- Very good. ja?
Ja.
I'm gonna play it adagio.
You know. for the music and the poetry.
All art aspires to music.
- I like it.
- Yeah.
Sandwich!
What is this dolly doing here?
[crowd clamoring]
Sir! Sir. sir! Sir. can I borrow that?
[gunshot]
[Manny] All right. you motherfuckers!
Any of you don't work
gets a bullet in the fucking skull!
Get back to work! Get back to work!
Get back to work!
Manuel's great!
- How's that for camera?
- [crew member] Much better. Ruth.
Jesus Christ!
Is somebody gonna fix her face?
- Get her out of here!
- Fuck's sake.
- Do you not know how to do makeup?
- You. what's your name?
- Tim.
- Tim. you're fired.
- What?
- You heard her! Get the fuck off this set!
[suspenseful music playing]
[director] Action!
[crowd yelling]
[in German] Faster! Faster! Faster!
Faster! Faster. motherfuckers!
[suspenseful music ends abruptly]
- [typewriter keys clacking]
- [Elinor] "Marbled meadows metamorphose"
- "into the medieval plains of Iberia."
- [dramatic music playing]
"Soldiers swarm the fields
like flecks of paint from a madman's brush"
as your humble servant bears witness
"to the latest of the moving picture's
magic tricks."
[intense music playing]
Oh. why do I bother?
Look at these idiots!
I knew Proust. you know.
[intense music ends abruptly]
He's dead.
He did have a drinking problem.
[George] That's true.
Probably ran into it himself. huh?
[crew member] It's a disease.
- [dramatic music playing]
- [men yelling]
[Manny] Your coffee. Mr. Thalberg.
Gracias.
- [swords clashing]
- [men shouting]
[Jack] Close with Swanson
and the fireworks. The end!
Irv! For the Clayton movie…
Sir. I think your tent's
in the line of fire.
- They'll edit it out in post.
- But I think we could get hurt...
Jack. every time you wear
a prosthetic. we lose money.
- [Jack] Don't be a pussy. Irv.
- The fireworks shot is too expensive.
- And you'll never get Gloria Swanson.
- Why no Swanson?
- She only does leads.
- [Abby] She's on the phone. sir.
- Thanks. Abby.
- [Irv] Who?
- [Abby] Gloria Swanson.
- [Irv] What?
Gloria? Jack Conrad.
Listen. I need some advice.
You know all
the young up-and-comers.
Well. I need a real discovery
for the part in my movie.
Who do you suggest?
Why discovery?
Well. this role requires real range.
A range I just don't see
in any of today's stars...
Excuse me.
Props needs better ranging. goddamn it!
We talked about this!
Sorry. what... No. I didn't...
Gloria. you have buckets of charm.
This is real drama we're talking about.
Shakespeare-level stuff.
Of course you could do Shakespeare.
You would be spectacular
in one of his fluffier plays.
Gloria. you're taking this the wrong way.
Well. I'd like to work with you too.
No. I'm afraid it's impossible.
It's gotta be a discovery.
We couldn't afford star fees
even if we wanted to.
Really? Huh.
Well. how about
I talk it over with the studio?
I can't speak for them.
of course. but I'll do my best.
Okay. then. Bye now.
She'll do it for cheap.
Now take the money I saved you
and put it towards
the goddamn fireworks shot.
- Cut!
- [dramatic music ends abruptly]
These fucking horses!
[groans] Motherfuckers!
Is that the last one?
- What happened?
- We lost all ten cameras.
But what about Jack's scene?
We make a camera run right now!
It's too far! Sun sets in three hours!
Send Joey now. You tell him
to speed. In the meantime...
Joey has a flag sticking
through his chest. Larry.
- A flag?
- He ran into it himself.
All right. Send Miguel then.
Here. 1312 Cahuenga.
You give 'em that card.
you tell 'em you work for Munn.
And hurry!
[Ruth] Okay. here's the shot.
Flirt with the men. Dance.
Get up on the table and that's it.
Just. don't look
at the fucking camera. Places!
- And camera!
- [camera whirring]
[Ruth] And music!
[upbeat music playing]
[Ruth] Action!
Hi. boys.
Santa. get me wet.
Another. please.
That one's for you. snuggle pup.
Hey. baby grand.
[man groans]
[chuckles]
Where are you going?
[upbeat music ends abruptly]
Uh. okay. Start dancing. please.
[upbeat music resumes playing]
[Jack] Bauhaus.
You know what I mean
by Bauhaus. don't you?
Not as it relates to this. sir. no.
[glass shattering]
[men clamoring]
And then he says.
"Hasta la vista. motherfucker."
Type it.
[men cheering and whistling]
[groans]
[shouting in Spanish]
And then he says.
"Frankly. Scarlett. you're a cunt."
Type it.
[men cheering]
- [men groan]
- [glass shatters]
Cut!
- [upbeat music ends abruptly]
- [tires screech]
Man number three. I can see your erection.
All right. tuck it. Just tuck it up.
[pants]
Hi. I work for Mr. George Munn.
We need a camera for Strassberger's show.
Oh. yeah? What kind of camera?
Bell and Howell 35 millimeter.
Uh-huh. Is it a 2708 model or 2709?
[hesitates] I'm not sure.
Is there a big difference?
Um… Yeah.
Hey. Donny!
[Donny] What?
There's a guy up here.
wants to know if there's a big difference
between a 2708 and a 2709. [chuckles]
- Okay.
- [Donny guffawing]
- Do you have either?
- Nope.
- Every camera's been loaned out.
- Fuck.
One's coming back in half an hour. though.
Half hour?
But it's a 2709.
Está bien. Okay.
Thirty minutes.
- For the 2709.
- I can do that. Thirty minutes.
- Two-seven…
- [Manny] Okay.
…zero-nine.
[clock ticking]
Are you married?
- My wife died.
- Oh. I'm dreadfully sorry.
[Ruth] Hey! Next part.
Miss Moore'll come in.
She saved you from prostitution
back in the day
so when you see her. cry in shame.
- I need big tears! Big! You got it?
- Okay. yeah.
[Ruth] Okay. Is that gum?
Are you fucking kidding me?
What's wrong with you?
Five-minute warning for Miss Moore!
[clock ticking]
- [door opens]
- [car horn honking]
That's mine!
I have 20 minutes to be in Simi Valley.
Which road do I take?
You're gonna look
at least 90 in this traffic.
We've got an eight-part sign-out process.
Let me go try to find a pen.
[upbeat music playing]
Action!
- And action. Miss Moore.
- [men cheering]
[Ruth] Hand on chest. Aghast!
My goodness. what is going on here?
[Ruth] Girl on bar. look at Miss Moore.
And tears!
[camera whirring]
Okay. glycerin.
- Um. we seem to be out.
- What? We haven't used any.
Porky thought it was lube.
- [Ruth] He thought it was lube?
- [Max] Yes.
[Ruth] Are you fucking... She can't cry.
She's just some random whore
from Wallach's house!
- [sobs]
- [upbeat music fades]
- Cut.
- [sniffs]
Hiya. I'm Nellie LaRoy.
- So we going again?
- [upbeat music playing]
[Otto] Fucking motherfucker.
I'm so sorry. God.
You gave us the beautiful light.
and I squandered it.
I won't have any fucking light now.
Otto. you should have fought
for 20 cameras. you idiot!
[siren wailing]
What is this bullshit?
[Manny] Camera! Camera!
Camera! Yeah.
Camera! Camera! Yeah.
My camera's here! My camera's here!
We roll. we roll! We are losing the light!
[Ruth] Take two! Action!
- [gasps]
- [Ruth] And cry!
[sobs]
Cut! Okay. I want to try something.
Think you could hold for two beats
for tears gushing?
So. eyes water for two. on the third beat.
I'm gonna do a light effect.
- and that's when you gush.
- Water for two. gush on three.
- Yep.
- Yes. Okay.
- Let's do it!
- Ruth. any notes on my entrance?
You're fine.
Ready for you. Mr. Conrad.
[Ruth] Action!
- [gasps]
- [Ruth] Eyes water.
Light. And tears!
Cut!
Okay. Forgive the ask. This is nuts.
But could you. by any chance.
try the same thing with less tears?
One tear or two?
- [upbeat music ends abruptly]
- [grunts]
Let's do this.
[in British accent] 'Twas brillig
and the slithy toves were…
[speaking normally] Oh. hey. Come with.
- [man] Camera's up the hill. Mr. Conrad.
- [Jack] Over here?
There? Yeah.
We'd better hurry.
[Jack grunting]
There? Okay.
[Otto] My beautiful baby boy.
Come. come. Okay. right here. Right there.
Now remember. you are sad and lonely man.
Right here.
No one will ever love you but her.
and she's only in your head. okay?
- [man] Last looks!
- Do I know her?
[Otto] No. She's in your head!
No. no! No last looks! No last looks!
Get the fuck out! I'll fucking kill you!
We are losing the light!
We roll now! We roll!
Roll. roll. roll. roll.
[retching. burping]
[Otto] Music!
[soft music playing]
And action.
- [Ruth] Action!
- [gasps]
[man] Oh. my God. it's a fire!
Everyone. run! Run!
[Ruth] Don't stop the camera!
Keep rolling! Keep rolling!
Single tear!
- Cannon!
[Ruth] More crying!
Now laugh in embarrassment.
Now look at Miss Moore.
You're trying to hide the shame.
- Hold steady.
- What the...
[Ruth] You're trying to be strong.
You're trying to bury the pain.
But you can't hold back
that one final tear!
[music rises]
[music fades out]
- And cut.
- Cut.
We got it.
[all cheering. applauding]
Who the fuck is that?
Camera boy! The camera boy!
You saved my movie!
I love you! I love you!
Yes! Did you see that?
Did you see the butterfly?
That was a butterfly.
Who's writing the titles on this?
- I gotta ask you something.
- Yeah? Was it okay?
It was incredible!
I just... How do you do it?
Just tear up over and over
like it's nothing?
I just think of home.
[upbeat music playing]
[Elinor] So. Jacky boy.
how do you think it turned out?
People want the kiss.
we give them the kiss.
But. madame. I can't help but wonder.
don't we have a higher calling?
[Don] We got a lot of great stuff.
We're really excited
about our new discovery. Nellie LaRoy.
Is she here tonight?
Can you point her out to me?
- Uh…
- [Nellie cheering]
Yeah. she's the one having sex
with the ice sculpture.
We're all very fond of her.
[Jack] It needs more punch.
Take two frames off the tail
and three more off the head.
- Manuel.
- Yes?
I saw Olga Putti sing
to herself in Hungarian.
and I think I'm in love.
Send two dozen roses to her dressing room
every morning this week.
- You know she doesn't speak English?
- Neither does love.
Let's do a title here.
"I've been in fashion shows too."
"They voted me
the 'Least Dressed Woman' in Paris."
And when it looks like the guy
asks her something.
have him ask her name and have her reply.
"No names. Just call me the wild child."
Do you think she swings both ways?
[woman] You're not on the list.
[Nellie] Okay. listen to me.
My name is Nellie LaRoy.
- Still not on the list.
- [Nellie] Lady. I'm in the movie.
They clearly cut you. baby.
Is that snakeskin?
Oh. my God! Nellie LaRoy!
Can I have an autograph?
I once fought a rattlesnake.
and it's against the law
- to even deal with a rattlesnake.
- [fan] Gorgeous! Gorgeous!
[Robert] There are laws now because
I fought the rattlesnake and lived.
Okay. You can go in.
Why. thank you.
[upbeat music ends abruptly]
[inaudible dialogue]
[audience laughing]
[audience applauding]
[audience cheering]
[triumphant music playing]
Naturally. I always knew
my daughter had it in her.
We're gonna do great things together.
she and I.
By the way. the name is Robert Roy.
She added the "La." [chuckles]
[radio announcer] It's celebration time
for Jack Conrad.
The epic Blood & Gold has confirmed Jack
as the highest-grossing
leading man in the world.
And now he's got his nuptials to toast.
this time with the Hungarian vixen.
Olga Putti.
One unlucky girl who did not
attend the festivities.
a Kansas teenager who.
overcome by the combined effect
of Valentino's death
and Conrad's fifth betrothal.
slit her wrists at home.
How sad.
Meanwhile. that new favorite.
Nellie LaRoy.
is making other girls
with California dreams
Roy-ally jealous!
Kinoscope's reteaming
the firecracker from Jersey
with Constance Moore.
And you know what that means.
"Moore" delightful chemistry
with Constance and Nellie!
This goddamn bitch is stealing
the scene right from under me!
She's changing the blocking
with every take.
She's icing her nipples
so they perk up through her dress.
Fuck you. I ain't icing my nipples.
This is natural.
You're just sore because
yours look like fucking latkes.
And she placed this in my dressing room.
- I don't even know what that is.
- [Constance groans]
Guys. let's just try a take. okay?
I don't think she meant anything by it.
- Let's go back to our ones.
- I need a drink. Whore!
Nellie. back to your one.
Guys. back to your one.
I'll give you something to cry about!
[Max] All right. we're going again!
[Ruth] Action!
Stop! She's changed the blocking again!
- Fine. Grab a close-up.
- [Constance] No! No close-up.
To match-cut with yours.
I'm the star! I get the close-up.
This is my money.
My company's writing the checks.
I decide!
Fine. Close-up on Constance.
Close-up on Constance!
Hi. Dr. Lubin.
I think I want to get
that operation we discussed.
Tonight.
Oh. my God.
How long will that take to heal?
What do you say we come in
for my close-up now?
"Common and uncouth though she may be."
there's something about her
that speaks to us in a language
"as vital and as bracing as life itself."
[Max] All right. you heard her.
Close-up on Nellie.
[Elinor] "Never have I seen
such a maelstrom of bad taste"
and sheer magic."
"Your humble servant bears witness."
"She has killed our grandmothers.
and we thank her for it."
- [camera shutter clicks]
- [music ends abruptly]
How much?
Jack!
It's Billy. Remember?
Yeah. Hi.
[urinating]
You should come by the Warners' lot.
Haven't seen you there in a while.
Yeah.
Jolson's sound picture's real good.
Sound picture?
Yeah.
Like Don Juan?
- [urinal flushing]
- No. no. no. no. Singing.
Talking pictures. Like you're there.
Not like the shorts.
- Really?
- Yeah. It's wild.
We did a screening on the lot last week.
People went nuts.
You think people want that. though?
Sound in their movies?
[forceful defecating and farting]
Yeah. why wouldn't they?
[Jack] This is
what we've been looking for!
Sound is how we redefine the form. Sound!
- [Olga screaming in Hungarian]
- Sweetie. I don't...
I don't know what you're upset about.
I don't understand Hungarian.
I heard Warners' screening last week
was a train wreck.
Manuel. what's she saying?
I got him learning Hungarian
'cause he's good with languages.
Something about
"getting fucked by a wheelbarrow
- "of monkeys."
- Geez Louise!
Olga?
Does this mean you don't like
the rain machine I made you?
She missed the rain in Budapest
so I built a rain machine in the garden.
- Hiccups that last ten years?
- Manuel?
- Something about…
- [Jack] Took ten years
- for the Wrights' airplane to work.
- …a horse's cock and your anus.
- Didn't it?
- [telephone ringing]
- That's not the same thing.
- Didn't it? Aha!
- That's not the same.
- [Jack] Why not?
Progress comes in fits.
- Hello?
- Spurts and fits.
[Manny] Thalberg.
People go to movies
not to listen to the noise.
- Irv?
- [Irv] Jack.
[screaming in Hungarian]
I wanna know about the Al Jolson movie.
Get Manuel to New York.
Send him to the Warners' Theatre
to see the premiere
and have him report back.
[Irv] Jolson? All right.
Who is that screaming?
That's just Olga. [chuckles]
Look. don't stand in the way of progress.
Irv. Sound is the future.
- Whoa! Hey! Holy shit!
- Send Manuel to New York.
- Jack! Jack. get down!
- Sweetie. sweetie.
Is this about Greta?
You know she's just a friend.
- [Manny] Get down! Jack!
- [gun cocking]
[Irv] What the fuck was that?
Hello? Hello?
Jack? Jack?
- [car horns honking]
- [indistinct chatter]
- Jack?
- [man] Nellie!
- I got the ticket to the premiere.
- [woman] Nellie! Nellie. I love you!
I know. I'll let you know how it is.
[woman] Nellie! Nellie!
[indistinct clamoring]
Yes. Jack.
Yeah. okay. Bye.
[woman 1] Please. Nellie!
Nellie. please can I have your autograph?
[woman 2] Nellie! Nellie!
Nellie!
Manny!
[woman 3] Please. Nellie!
[man 1] Show me your tits.
you fucking bitch!
- [man 2] Right here!
- [man 3] Stop. stop. stop!
- [man 4] You fucking whore!
- [woman 4] I love you.
[Manny] No. no. no! Back off. cabrones!
Back off now!
Nellie!
Tony. go. go!
- [chuckles]
- How you been?
[gentle music playing]
- Good. good.
- Ah! Look at you!
- Wow.
- You remember me.
Yeah. of course I remember you.
How could I forget?
- And you're a star now.
- I was always a star. remember?
- Right. right.
- [chuckles]
And what are you doing here?
Are you here for a movie or…
No. I had to get out of town
for a few days.
Some shit came up with a guy
saying I owed him money
in a game of craps.
Then Wallach got pissed.
He straightened him out.
but he thinks I have a gambling problem.
which I don't.
I only gamble if I'm.
you know. pissed or drunk
or having a great night.
What about you?
Jack Conrad sent me.
- Jack Conrad? Oh!
- Yeah. I'm working with him.
I would fuck him. Wow.
Why would Conrad send you here? God.
I got out of this place
first chance I got.
Took nothing with me but my dad.
He's actually my business manager now.
- He is?
- Yeah. He's so bad at it.
- Cannot add. cannot spell.
- Why don't you hire someone else?
He's my dad. What else is he gonna do?
Oh. shit. we're here. Hey. Tony?
Can you hang onto this
for me. please? Thanks.
I'm just gonna be a minute. okay?
Actually. do you wanna come in with me?
Yeah.
[gentle music concluding]
- [nurse] May I help you?
- Yes. Nellie LaRoy.
Hi.
Seems okay here.
It's pretty nice.
This is Manny.
He works in the movies too.
All right. Thank you.
That was a waste of time. [chuckles]
Let's go.
I hate when people put fucking toppings
on ice cream.
Doesn't need it.
Just messes up a good thing.
You know what I mean?
I fucking hate that.
God. I've never done nothing
except disappoint people my whole life.
Teachers told me I was no good.
Boys told me I was no good.
Every fucking casting director
in the city told me
I was too short or I was too fat.
Usually I was too fat.
You know. my mama actually
had some fat years too.
You wouldn't know it now.
looking at her. but she did.
They fucked up with me. Manny.
They really fucked up with me.
'Cause I make 'em squirm.
And I like making 'em squirm.
Let 'em know that I got here
on my terms. not theirs.
And when I'm done.
I'm gonna dance my ass off into the night.
And they'll know...
Everyone will fucking know
that they could never control
one goddamn fucking thing.
Do you like ice cream?
Of course.
My family lives in L.A.. you know.
Really?
I thought they were in Mexico.
We crossed the border when I was 12.
They're not far.
I could take a car. drive for 30 minutes
and just say hi.
But you never do.
Sí.
It's just easier to be on my own.
[gentle music playing]
I've always been on my own.
Tony. take Manny wherever he needs to go.
- Oh. no. it's okay.
- No. no. no. I insist. I insist.
I'm gonna see you back in L.A.. okay?
[gentle music concludes]
[movie dialogue playing softly]
[Al Jolson] Dirty hands. dirty face.
Little devil. that's what they say.
♪ But to me ♪
♪ He's an angel ♪
♪ Of joy ♪
[audience cheering and clapping]
[Al Jolson] Wait a minute. wait a minute.
You ain't heard nothin' yet.
Wait a minute. I tell ya.
You ain't heard nothing.
You wanna hear "Toot. Toot. Tootsie"?
["Toot Toot Tootsie! (Goo' Bye)" playing]
♪ Toot. toot. tootsie. goodbye ♪
♪ Toot. toot. tootsie. don't cry ♪
[audience member] Oh. my God! Oh. my God!
♪ That takes me away from you… ♪
[Manny] Jack? It's Manny.
Everything's about to change.
["Toot Toot Tootsie! (Goo' Bye)"
concludes]
Nell. how you feeling?
I'm ready.
- Yeah. you gonna try a take?
- Yeah.
Okay. so we're gonna pre-roll first.
I'll cue your entrance.
First mark is where you say the line.
"Hello. college."
and then you head to the phone.
do the rest of the dialogue.
- Sounds easy.
- I think it will be.
Lloyd. any direction on voice?
- Uh. no. We're good up here. Ruth.
- Okay. great.
Mark. can we fix her makeup?
Mark.
- No air conditioning? [chuckles]
- It's too loud.
Okay.
Just be natural. You'll be fine.
[Max] All right. places. everyone!
[bell rings]
Hey. whoa. what is that?
[Max] Harry. what kind of shoes
are those?
Come on. guys. rubber soles!
Okay. everyone. a reminder.
Rubber soles only from now on!
Okay.
And camera! And sound!
"It's Joanne from 31 Grimes Hall.
I just... "
Fuck! "Thirty-one Grays Hall."
Grays Hall. Grays Hall.
"Hiya. this is Joanne from 31 Grays Hall."
"I just wanted to see
if the phone worked."
"Just wanted to see if the phone worked.
Who is this?"
- Scene 17. take one.
- [Bill] Mark.
[whispering] Come on. Come on.
come on. come on. You know it.
[Ruth] And action!
[heart beating]
[camera whirring]
[door creaking]
[lights buzzing]
Hello. college!
- [microphone feedback]
- Jesus. fuck! Cut!
- [bell rings]
- [Max] What happened?
[Lloyd] She blew the valves.
- I just need a minute.
- [Max] All right. well. hurry.
- Give me one sec.
- Christ. it's hot in there.
[Max] Okay. are we still in places?
Okay.
- Okay. all set here. Miss LaRoy?
- Yeah.
What would really help us
would be if you said the line.
like. a little more quietly.
- Okay.
- [Max] All right. places. everyone!
And camera!
- And sound!
- [bell rings]
Close that!
Don't you know what a red light means?
Scene 17. take two.
[Bill] Mark.
Action.
- Cut. Missed your mark. Nell.
- [bell rings]
- [Nellie] Oh.
- [Ruth] It's…
Yeah. I…
I don't know. I felt. like.
a little lighter on my feet that time.
I feel I should come
further into the room.
[Ruth] Right. but the microphone is…
- All right. Hey. Lloyd?
- [Lloyd] Yeah.
Can we just move the mic
a little deeper in the room?
[Lloyd] Why?
Because Nellie felt
lighter on her feet that time.
[Nellie] I was just saying I think
I should come further into the room.
Okay. Yeah. sure. I mean.
if you have half an hour to spare.
- [Ruth] Half an hour?
- Well. I can't just move the mic.
I have to redo all the wires.
We'll have to reset the rafters.
then find the new position.
Then I'm gonna have to recalibrate
- the whole room.
- Okay. okay. okay.
Nell. why don't we just... Is it okay...
Let's just try one on the mark.
You can do it.
- And camera! And sound!
- [bell rings]
- Scene 17. take three.
- [Bill] Mark.
Action.
- Well. hello. college.
- Cut! No good for sound.
Well. fucking hell. Lloyd.
Could you just let us
get through one take?
Why would I do that
if you won't be able to use it?
You told me to do it quiet.
- That's why I did it quiet.
- Quiet. not inarticulate.
You can't mumble.
This is bullshit.
Are we going again or what?
- I can't breathe in here!
- We're going again!
- And camera and sound!
- [bell rings]
- Scene 17. take four.
- [Bill] Mark.
Action.
Well. hello. college!
- Motherfucker!
- Who opened the door?
[crew members shouting]
[Max] All right. everybody. eyes on me!
Any other faggots
who ignore that red light…
I'm sorry. you're alternating the pitch
of your voice too much.
- Okay. can you just...
- Lloyd. Lloyd. fuck off.
Fuck off.
I listen to my fucking director.
not the fucking sound guy!
Who the fu...
Mr. Wallach. so happy
you're joining us. Come on.
Maybe try staying more monotone.
Okay.
- [Max] And camera and sound!
- Yeah. okay.
Scene 17. take five.
- [Bill] Mark.
- Action.
Well. hello. college.
- Hiya. this is Joanne from Gray...
- Cut!
Motherfucking shit!
Cocksucking... What the fuck?
[Ruth] What the fuck happened now?
- I'm hearing a high-pitched noise.
- Yeah. it's her voice.
- Do you hear that?
- [Ruth] For fuck's sake.
Do you hear? That squeak?
Is anybody wearing a watch?
- No.
I'm telling you.
I can't stay in there that long.
- It's a fucking hotbox!
- I get it. Bill.
- Nobody is comfortable in here.
- Quiet!
What is that fucking sound?
- We gotta move this along.
- [whispers] I'm so sorry. Mr. Wallach.
We'll get this under control.
I promise you.
"Hiya. this is Joanne
from 31 Grimes Hall."
Fuck! Grays Hall.
"I just wanted to see... Who is this?"
Hey. Count? Count?
- I need a red one.
- Yeah. yeah.
"The" Count. It's just The Count.
Just next time say. "The Count."
Now's not really "The" fucking time.
Found it! It's a pin in Ruth's ankle.
Did you have surgery?
If you can just keep
your right leg absolutely still.
[Max] And camera and sound!
- Scene 17. take six.
- [Bill] Mark.
Action.
- Well. hello. college.
- [sneezes]
Who sneezed? Who the fuck sneezed?
Kike-nosed. Hymie-hole
piece of Mongoloid shit!
I see you.
Oh. I see you right there.
you little Shylock dickface.
Wipe your nose again!
Wipe your little hook nose.
you menorah motherfucker!
Now. does anyone else here
need to sneeze? Huh?
Does anyone else here need
to fuck this scene in the ass?
Camera! And sound!
- Scene 17. take seven.
- [Bill] Mark.
Action.
- Hello. college.
- Nell. your mark!
[screams] Fuck this shit!
- Fuck. Lloyd.
- It's a million fucking degrees!
We gotta move the mic.
Or you could fucking direct her
to hit her fucking mark.
- But why is it so fucking hard?
- Oh. you're right!
I didn't realize we were making Ben-Hur!
I can move it right now.
My whole year is wide open.
I mean. we could shoot this thing
through fucking New Year's.
Wherever the fuck those
little feet of hers want to go.
I can move the mic for them!
- Okay. calm down!
- Get off of me! I dare you!
I fucking dare you!
- Get off the set!
- You're good. you're good.
Un-fucking-professional!
[Ruth] Okay. Lloyd. ready to go again?
You want me to use this chalk?
I could make the mark bigger for you?
- [Ruth] Okay. we're gonna go again.
- [Lloyd] It's fine. No. it's fine.
- The mark's right here.
- I'm gonna kick your fucking ass!
Oh. yeah! Come on! Come on!
[Bill] Can we go?
I'm gonna have a fucking
heart attack in here.
Get back in your fucking box. Bill!
[Lloyd] I can't even believe this.
Everyone. shut up!
Fucking shut the fuck up!
[Nellie] That's not how we make movies.
Shut the fuck up!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut the fuck up!
Now. if anyone stops this scene again.
I will shit on you!
I will shit in your mouth. I promise you!
Is that clear. Lloyd?
Is that good for fucking sound?
Now. we are going again!
Camera! And motherfucking sound!
- [bell rings]
- Scene 17. take eight.
[Bill] Mark.
Action.
Hello. college.
Hello?
Hiya. this is Joanne from 31 Grays Hall.
I was just gonna see if the phone worked.
Who is this?
You don't say. The dean!
Well. how you doin'?
It's a nice campus you got here.
So…
what's a girl supposed to do
once she's here?
[chuckles] Sure. classes.
But ain't you got any parties?
Not till the evening. huh?
All right. I can handle that.
I'm from Granville. Ohio.
so I know quiet. [chuckles]
Thanks a bunch. Dean. See you later.
Nice fella. Wonder if he's single.
Cut! Cut!
[all cheering]
[sobs] Yes!
Yes!
- Okay. check the gate!
- [Max] Billy. check the gate!
Billy! [chuckles]
Bill!
Billy. come on.
Bill... Let's get a crowbar.
Come on. Hurry up.
- Bill!
- [screaming]
[Ruth] Oh. my God.
He's dead.
[upbeat music playing]
[Jack] Manuel!
Meet Estelle.
She's from Broadway. She's a real actor.
We got engaged yesterday.
Now she's trying to explain to me
that movies are a low art.
Mucho gusto. Drinks?
- Double shot of tequila.
- Water. darling.
Hola. Jacky!
Hola. Carmelita.
I have no idea who that is.
The point is. darling.
I believe movies are every bit
as profound.
And with sync sound. which. who knows.
could be what the discovery of perspective
was for painting.
I think what we have here
in Hollywood is high art.
- It's...
- Party time. sparkle cocks!
Hot damn!
- Jack Conrad?
- [Jack] Hmm?
You are even more fuckable in person.
Thank you.
This is Estelle.
- His fiancée.
- Fiancée?
Hey. I'm not actually gonna fuck him.
I beat the whole USC football team
at a game of craps when we wrapped.
and so now they have to be
my slaves for the whole night.
- Jack. can you say hi to my dad. please?
- Sure.
He wanted to meet you.
He's also my manager.
It's a good thing we met. Jack.
I got a business proposition just for you.
A Nellie-themed diner.
I'm gonna call it "The Wild Child Grill."
I'm gonna serve sandwiches
shaped like her face.
[Sidney] It's not a threat.
it's just what it is.
If you keep playing flat.
I'm gonna fucking headbutt you.
and it's just gonna be what it's gonna be.
You need to play better.
You embarrassing us.
Joe. you hear what he just said to me?
Listen to this psychopath.
When you gonna do something?
Why you worried about Joe doing something?
Nigga. when are you gonna do something?
Have you ever heard of Alexander Scriabin?
Why the fuck do I care
about Alexander Scriabin?
Alexander Scriabin was a Russian pianist.
Broke his hands just so his fingers
could stretch across the keys better.
I'm saying if I fucking headbutt you
across them funky-ass lips of yours.
you might start playing a little better.
- We can hope.
- You're fucking deranged. Sidney.
Elinor's trying to civilize me
for talkies. Ain't that nice?
"Isn't that nice?"
- Isn't.
- And more attire next time.
A little more attire's always in the way.
Nellie dresses low 'cause Nellie is low.
Now. let me tell you about the time
I fought a rattlesnake.
It was Death Valley. April.
Jack? It's George.
Ah. Georgie.
Who was it this time?
[George] Claire.
Claire. Well. Claire's a lesbian.
That's an uphill battle for anyone.
Come on. buddy.
get your head out of there.
- Let's go get a drink.
- [George] Okay. okay. I'll stop.
I'm stuck.
- What?
- [George] I'm stuck.
Get me the fuck out of here!
[Sidney] Ladies and gentlemen.
your attention. please!
For your entertainment this evening.
Miss Lady Fay Zhu
will now choose a partner.
[tango music playing]
Hi.
I'm Nellie LaRoy's dad.
[chuckles]
What's your name?
Cannonball!
[laughs]
- [music fades out]
- [audience clapping]
[Irv scats]
You're great. man.
You call my office. 'cause we're gonna
need more musicians.
And you're talented. man.
Mr. Thalberg. it's an honor to meet...
Yeah. I'm gonna go throw up now.
[man 1] Spoke to my friend at Kinoscope.
He said the movie's a disaster.
- [man 2] LaRoy's?
- [man 1] Yeah.
They went double the budget
'cause she could never hit
her fucking mark
- and her voice sounds like a dying pig.
- [men laughing]
[man 1] No. seriously. apparently
the footage is so awful.
Wallach's already thinking
about dumping her.
[man 2] I'm not surprised.
She never had any talent anyway.
[man 1] Oh. my God. Zero.
Filthy. slutty piece of fucking trash
with a nasty voice.
[man 2 laughing]
- [man 1] You meet her dad?
- [man 2] Oh. my God.
He's even more embarrassing
than she is. Fucking idiot.
[man 1 chuckling]
- Goodbye!
- [man 2 laughing]
[man 1] Don't come back!
[man 1] It's the end. I'm telling you.
It's the end for all of 'em.
All the frogs.
[sobbing. sniffling]
[whispers] Don't be a fucking baby.
[upbeat music playing]
[Robert] And that. that is
when I grabbed the snake by the head.
- The big fucking man! Here he is!
- What?
What's he telling you?
What was he saying to you?
- The snake story.
- Come on. buddy.
- [indistinct chatter]
You got it. yeah. [chuckles]
[Nellie] Dad. I have an idea.
Why don't you fight a snake.
a real one. right now?
- Come on.
- Okay. no problemo.
- Let's go fight a snake.
- [Nellie] Okay!
Fucking listen up.
all you big-dick mister men!
Who wants to see my dad
fight a fucking snake?
Fuck yeah!
[crowd cheers]
[Jack] A snake's getting fought!
[all] A snake's getting fought!
[upbeat music concludes]
Yeah. I mean. Chaplin is hung for sure.
but Gary Cooper.
Gary Cooper is a fucking horse!
He's also a fucking pussy.
All that cock. no balls.
A shame.
What are the schlongs like on Broadway?
You want some?
- [Estelle] No. thank you.
- Ah. it doesn't look that bad. buddy.
- Stop!
- [banging on window]
[tires screech]
[snake rattles]
Sweetie. come on.
[indistinct chatter. laughter]
[Elinor] Please. hurry!
This can't be where we... Where are we?
[man 1] Where'd he go?
[man 2] Holy fuck!
Out of my way! [grunts]
No! Stand... Stand... Stand back!
Back!
I'm gonna fight a snake.
Whoo!
[chuckles] Look. sweetie.
he's gonna fight a snake.
- Isn't this great?
- [Robert] Here we go.
[grunts]
See that snake? See this man?
Watch this.
So. first.
one must assume
the position of a mongoose! [growls]
[hisses. clicks teeth]
[slurring] I'm not...
I'm just gonna... [growls]
[babbling] Tell... Tell me that…
If I could just've done the whole thing
over and over and over!
If I could just fucking defend...
Yeah... Fighting…
[mumbling]
If I could just… just…
I...
- [groans. laughs]
- [crowd cheers]
[laughter]
Motherfucker!
Who is gonna fight it?
[indistinct chatter]
- I got practice.
- [man 3] I'm allergic.
God damn it. you fucking pussies!
You fucking piece-of-shit.
fucking bullshit. fucking pussies!
The night is almost over.
I got a 10:00 a.m. call time.
I just want to see
a motherfucking snake fight!
- Nellie. babe...
- Don't "Nellie. babe" me.
you six-foot fucking vagina!
[crowd laughs]
I will fight it!
- [crowd] No. no. no!
- [Jack] Yes!
- I'm more man than any of you.
- Nellie. Nellie.
- I ain't a fucking pussy!
- Nellie…
See? You see that?
It's that fucking easy!
You chickenshit...
[screams]
Nellie!
[crowd gasps. screams]
It's not letting go!
Nellie! Nellie!
Let it go. Let it...
Hey! Hey. I got it! [grunts]
- [gentle music playing]
- [snake rattles]
[screaming]
[Estelle] Jack!
Jack!
- [crowd clamoring fades]
- [music rises]
[Estelle] Jack!
Jack!
- Jack. do something!
- [crowd clamoring]
Right. Once more
into the breach. dear friends!
Once more!
- Ready! Hold your...
- [music ends abruptly]
[screams]
Jacky!
Help us!
For fuck's sake.
[sucking]
Welcome to the wonderful world of sound!
[upbeat music playing]
♪ I'm singin' in the rain
Just singin' in the rain ♪
♪ What a glorious feeling
I'm happy again ♪
♪ I'm laughing at clouds
So dark above… ♪
I have to do this?
[George] What do you mean?
It's gonna be great!
- Just stand there and sing?
- [George] Exactly.
- [Jack] While it's raining.
- [George] Yeah.
And that's Noah's ark?
Uh. I believe so. yeah.
[Jack] Because it's raining so much?
To be honest with you.
I don't really know why it's Noah's ark.
- Georgie.
- Come on.
- No. No. this is...
- What?
- Norma's here. Buster Keaton's here.
- George. no. No.
The song's a hit.
- [chuckles] Oh.
- You love to sing.
- Oh. I hate you. I hate you.
- Come on. [chuckles]
- Just don't let Olga shoot me.
- Okay.
♪ Just singing. just singin' in the rain ♪
♪ I'm singin' in the rain
Just singin' in the rain ♪
♪ What a glorious feeling
I'm happy again ♪
♪ I'm laughing at clouds
So dark up above ♪
♪ The sun's in my heart
And I'm ready for love ♪
♪ Let the stormy clouds chase
Everyone from the place ♪
♪ Come on with your rain
I've got a smile on my face ♪
[director] Cut! Cut!
Musicians. you're on a break.
I wanna work with my actors for a second.
The head bobbing.
it's very mechanical right now.
Think of something that makes it
personal to you. Okay?
That's a little too much. Mary.
That's too personal. Okay?
So just bobbing. all right?
Let's work on that.
Up. Up. Rest of the body doesn't move.
Up. up. up. up. up. up.
Very good. Mary. Up. up. up. up. up. up.
Oh. I like this. Isolate the shoulders.
What do you think?
[director] Up. up. up. up. up. up.
You're asking me what I think?
- [director] Okay.
- Yeah.
- [director] This looks so much better.
- [chuckles]
I think you got those cameras pointed
in the wrong direction.
[director] Do the rainbow. remember?
Big arms!
[Sidney] That's what I think.
We're gonna take this one more time.
Everybody ready? Musicians are ready?
- And action!
- [music resumes]
♪ I'm singin' in the rain
Just singin' in the rain ♪
♪ What a glorious feeling
I'm happy again… ♪
[director] Up. up. up. up. up. up.
Bob. bob. bob. bob. bob. That's better.
♪ The sun's in my heart
And I'm ready for love ♪
[director] Good. Good. good.
Candace. Very good.
[singing continues]
[director] Yeah. it's coming together.
This is much better.
Remember that energy.
[music concludes]
[director] Cut!
[bell rings]
Good idea.
Manuel Torres.
How have you been?
Well. sir. And you?
You want to talk with Mr. Thalberg?
Were these Sid Palmer shorts your idea?
They're more like a collaboration
between Sidney and me.
Uh-huh. How'd you like to leave MGM.
come be sound chief at Kinoscope?
What?
We need Spanish-language pictures.
We're taking new directions.
- It's changing times. Manny.
- [Manny] I'm honored. sir. but…
And we need to do something
about Nellie LaRoy.
Oh. yeah.
You know her. don't you?
The Jersey thing doesn't work anymore.
Today's audiences find her pornographic.
She's been hanging around
Jim McKay's casinos like a half-wit.
She owes gambling debts all over town.
And she sounds like a donkey.
I mean…
Anyways…
think about it.
[Manny] Gentlemen. here's the plan.
We turn Nellie LaRoy into a lady.
We change her parts. We fix her voice.
No more drugs. No more gambling.
Elinor St. John writes a story about
her amazing transformation.
With the right endorsements.
and with Elinor as an ally.
we can remake Miss LaRoy
into an actress of sophistication.
Like the ladies of MGM.
Next. Sidney Palmer.
Today's white audiences
want Negroes in their pictures.
Negro music. Negro voices.
So we bring Sidney to Kinoscope.
whatever he costs.
One moment. gentlemen. One moment.
Sidney Palmer. okay? Sidney Palmer.
[gentle music playing]
I was hoping I could introduce
the two of you.
Miss LaRoy. meet Mr. Torres.
Mr. Torres. meet Miss LaRoy.
Mr. Torres is gonna be working for us
here at Kinoscope.
Hi. Mr. Torres.
Just want you to know
that I'm ready to change.
and I'll do whatever you need.
Call me Manny.
- [gentle music concludes]
- [man] Cut!
- [upbeat music playing]
- Beautiful. Bellísimo. bellísimo.
Next time. try softer. okay?
"But why. my darling Pierre? Why?"
Walt! Walt. hey!
Move that microphone 45 degrees. okay?
- That one near her. okay?
- [telephone rings]
A ver. no. no. no. Hey. [whistles] Amigo!
It's not Manuel. it's Manny. Manny Torres.
- Not Manuel. okay?
- [crew member] Phone for you. sir!
- Yeah.
- [speaking Spanish]
- Manny Torres.
- [Jack] Manuel.
- Moving up fast.
- Jack? I'm sorry.
- I meant to call you.
- The reds chill her out.
- Blues keep her skinny. okay?
- [Jack] Don't say a word.
- I'm happy for you. You deserve this.
- Did you see my screen test yet. Manny?
[Jack] Now go show those fat fucks
how it's done.
[receiver clicks]
Okay! Okay! Vamos. vamos.
ya. ya. ya. vamos!
Let's roll. people! Let's go! Take two!
"Pierre. who is the fella
to whom you are speaking?"
- "Who is the fellow." Fellow.
- [Nellie] Fellow. Fuck.
Welcome to your new home. Mr. Palmer.
And your car.
A gift from Mr. Wallach.
[assistant] And that finishes at 5:30.
leaving you enough time to make the gala.
[executive] And a Hearst invite
has come in for Miss LaRoy.
Only question is.
what do we do about Fay Zhu?
It won't help Nellie
with the Hearst crowd.
"Listen to me. Catherine.
I don't care if they find us."
"They could strip me of my rank
and it wouldn't change how I feel."
Latest voice tests.
Conrad Nagel. rich tone.
William Haines. good consonants.
[Manny] You're messing
with Nellie's career.
and we're trying so hard
to get it back on track.
There's a new sensibility now.
People care about morals.
"I've known loss. I've known pain.
You're what gives me life."
Try accenting "you"
a little more. darling.
"You are what gives me life."
Just a suggestion.
Marion Davies stutters a bit.
Maybe supporting roles from now on?
[Manny] This sort of thing
is no longer acceptable.
- "You are what gives me life."
- Maybe try it slower.
[Irving] Ramon Novarro can play guitar.
but south-of-the-border accent.
What I'm trying to say
is Kinoscope can no longer employ you.
Your image is not helpful.
and we don't need titles anymore.
That's it.
I'm sorry.
[Irving] Jack Conrad has a good voice.
is our biggest asset.
Also the most expensive.
- [knocking on door]
- Yeah?
[Jack] "You are what gives me life."
"I love you."
And what I'd suggest there would be to...
[telephone rings]
- [Jack] Hello?
- [Irv] Jack. it's Irv.
Listen. there's no good way to say this.
They found George in his home
this morning.
Looks like he struck out
- with a girl he was seeing.
- [music ends abruptly]
[Irv] He shot himself.
Jack?
Thank you.
So. what I would suggest there
would be to play subtext rather than...
Honey?
Are you okay?
He was the first one to say I have talent.
He saved my life.
[Estelle] Who?
It's not a low art. you know.
I want you to know that.
What I do means something
to millions of people.
My folks didn't have the money
or the education to go to the theater.
so they went to the vaudeville houses.
and then the nickelodeons.
And you know what? There's beauty there.
What happens up on that screen
means something.
Maybe not to you in your ivory tower.
But for real people on the ground.
it means something.
Jack. I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Of course you don't.
Of course you don't!
A hundred thousand people
see you on Broadway.
and it's the smash of the century. right?
Well. here it's a flop!
A fucking flop!
So do me a favor. darling.
Save your subtext recommendations
for your pretentious
Eugene O'Neill-Henrik Ibsen jerkoffs
that only a handful of rich geriatrics
give two fucks about.
and I'll do what I do without your help!
Huh?
[camera whirring]
Listen. Catherine.
I don't care if they find us.
They could strip me of my rank
and it wouldn't change how I feel.
I've known loss. I've known pain.
It's you who gives me life.
I love you.
- You think it works?
- It's great.
It's a winner. Jack.
You think it works?
I wish George could've seen it.
[man 1] Yes.
[knocking on door]
[man 2] Mr. Conrad.
you're gonna miss your train.
Christ!
[groans] Fuck.
I'm off to repair my marriage.
I'll see you bastards in a month.
[man 1] Good luck with that.
[Elinor] Okay. don't forget.
Your friend Manuel pulled
a lot of strings to get you in here.
These people choose
who stays and who goes.
So show them that you're
a lady of sophistication
and you'll be back on top.
So. now what did we discuss?
"-Ing" not "-in."
"Isn't" not "ain't."
And when in doubt. say somethin' French.
Perfection!
[Elinor] Also. no drinking.
and try not to eat too much.
- [soft orchestral music playing]
- Billy! Marion!
- Oh. Elinor!
- Hello.
May I please present to you
Miss Nellie LaRoy.
- [Marion] How do you do?
- Enchantée.
[Billy] Good evening. Miss LaRoy.
Nell. I'd like you
to also meet Mildred Yates.
Sir Delmer Lunny.
And Jonathan and Harriet Rothschild.
Pleasure.
[man 1] Gerald. have you heard about
the new Ellis Engel picture?
It sounds just awful.
[Gerald] Yes. I've spoken to L.B.
about it already.
There'll be no more of that kind of thing.
I can assure you.
Here we have a pâté de campagne
designed by Krümt with a Takagei bubble.
[Jonathan] I hear
it's Strindberg season in New York.
Do you like Miss Julie?
Yes. she is lovely and very talented.
[all laugh]
[chattering]
- Sidney.
- Manny.
All right.
Billy. is your new rug really a Klikó?
I got it last spring. One of a kind.
Mr. Palmer.
It is truly an honor to meet you.
Teddy and I saw Cottage Blues last week.
Genius!
Thanks.
Do you play bridge. Miss LaRoy?
[in French] The bread speaks English
with the dog young.
[Marion speaking French]
[Elinor speaking French]
[man 2] So you're from Mexico. then?
Spain. Madrid.
[man 2] Spain. Madrid. Wow.
How did you get into music. Mr. Palmer?
I taught myself. mostly.
Incredible. Who are your influences?
Scriabin.
I like Rachmaninoff.
Do you think George Eliot was better
as a novelist or as a poet. Nell?
[in English] I think he was marvelous.
marvelous at both. [chuckles]
Now I do apologize.
but I must resign briefly
to the powder room.
I shan't be long. Ta-ta!
Everything you need. you know. right here.
It's got the restaurants.
and of course. now you can't gamble
in L.A. You been to Cal-Neva?
This one guy McKay owns a few joints.
but he's a little scary. so...
- One moment. please.
- [man 2] Oh. sure.
Jack! Didn't think you'd get in in time.
How was Europe?
- Inspiring!
- And congrats on the new film.
- Opens tonight. right?
- Correct.
Did you know Michelangelo painted
the entire Sistine Chapel
on his back?
Manny! How's our girl doing?
- Oh. she's doing great. Perfect.
- Okay. good.
[Nellie] Manny. I need to go home.
- No. Nellie. you cannot go home.
- I can't do this.
- [Manny] You're going back out there.
- I'm having a heart attack.
Elinor and I worked so hard
to get you into this.
- Manny. I am dying out there.
- Okay. okay.
They're a bunch of... They're awful.
Mildred's got a fucking rabbit
on her shoulders
that's probably still alive.
- Hey.
- The ass-pincher!
- They can save your career.
- They don't like me!
- If they like you…
- They don't!
…we get the right director.
the right publicity...
What about Ruth? I need Ruth back.
Ruth doesn't fucking cut it anymore!
Listen to me. I'm here for you.
It's you and me.
You could be a star again.
Nellie. Again. It's you and me.
You look beautiful. okay?
- I look fucking ridiculous.
- What's your name?
- Nellie LaRoy.
- Perfect. Once again.
- In French.
- It is French already! [chuckles]
- Okay. let's go.
[Nellie] "Roy" means "king." remember?
Beautiful.
Jack. It's great to see you.
You. too. Salud.
Are you holding up?
Oh.
Well. I do miss him.
Uh…
Miss him?
George.
What were you referring to?
Jack. How was Europe?
Great! And good to be home.
That's the attitude.
Staying strong.
- Where have you been?
- She's fine.
And what do you think of the new wave
of race films. Mr. Palmer?
I find the studios' committees
for the casting of Negroes inspiring.
don't you?
[in English] And he replies.
"Do they need an electrician?"
[all laugh]
Do you know any good jokes. Nellie?
Yeah. I...
[in English] Nell prefers listening
to jokes rather than telling them.
- Come on. tell us a joke.
- I have a joke.
Harold Lloyd and I were in France…
Hey. how you holding up?
You. too?
Well. I guess the movie isn't a hit.
So be it.
I'm sure you'll get another chance.
Why wouldn't I get another chance?
No. it just... What I mean...
[Jack] Would someone kindly tell me
what the fuck is going on?
He shows up with a mime.
I go. "Harold. my croque monsieur is
worth a lot more than a mime!"
[laughter]
Nell. you must have some good ones.
Well. I am not the best joke teller.
[Jonathan] Come on. Nellie.
Isn't being funny what you do?
Yeah. I believe that films like yours
are a gentle
but virile olive branches
in these divided times.
That is actually my cue.
- I should be going.
- No. please. you must play for us.
[Billy] Come on. Nellie.
We'll approve your next picture.
- [Jonathan] Yes. Nellie. be funny.
- [Elinor] You know. I just thought of one.
Two fish are on their honeymoon...
Actually. I got one.
A bear and a rabbit are
shittin' in the woods one day.
And the bear says to the rabbit.
"Hey. do ya ever have a problem
with the shit stickin' to your fur?"
And the rabbit finishes shittin'
and he says.
"No. I never do. Why?"
And the bear says. "Fan-fuckin'-tastic!"
And he grabs the rabbit behind the ears
and…
- [music ends abruptly]
- [crowd gasps]
I can't believe you just…
Why not?
Why? Haven't you heard
what they say about me?
I'm a degenerate fucking animal.
"Oh. Nellie!" Look at them.
"Who knows what she might do?
She's from Jersey. you know."
This is what a degenerate fucking animal
from Jersey does.
[crowd gasping]
[munches loudly. grunts]
That's what the degenerate fuckin' animal
from Jersey does.
So you know what?
I'm gonna let you all go on
fucking your cousins.
polishing your guest lists.
plying your underaged fuckin' mistresses
with fuckin' Beaujolais.
you sick fucks!
I'm the animal? What is this shit?
What is this shit?
Oh. I'm the sick one!
I'm the fuckin' crazy one!
You people make me fucking sick!
You're not better than me!
You're not!
You're not fucking better than me.
I don't need this shit.
You know what? I'm gonna go home.
I'm gonna stick some coke up my pussy.
and you all can stick
your champagne flutes
up your rose-smellin'. candy-tastin'.
snow-white fuckin' assholes!
[stomach gurgling]
[crowd gasping]
[Hearst] My rug!
You puked on my rug!
[hushed murmuring]
[Catherine] Please. before it's too late.
You can't stay here. They'll find you.
They'll find us.
[Jack] Listen. Catherine.
I don't care if they find us.
They could strip me of my rank
and it wouldn't change how I feel.
I've known loss. I've known pain.
It's you who gives me life.
[snickers]
[Jack] Catherine…
I love you.
I love you. I love you. I love you.
[audience laughing]
- [man] "I love you. I love you!"
- [man 2] "I love you!"
[laughing]
[Elinor] Jack Conrad.
What are your thoughts for the future?
Well. my last two movies didn't work.
but I learned a lot from 'em.
There were things I'd taken for granted
that maybe I shouldn't have.
[Elinor] Well. you're still MGM's
biggest asset.
You still command the biggest paycheck.
And I'd like to earn it.
I'm still learning this new language.
[Elinor] Is it true
that you've quit drinking?
Yeah. It was getting in the way.
I'm not gonna let that happen anymore.
[Elinor] There's a lot of acting talent
coming in from the theater now.
Might you go to the stage
to gain more experience?
Elinor. I will master
the talking film on film.
[Elinor] Do you miss the silents?
No.
We shouldn't stand in the way of progress.
[Elinor] Okay. Thanks. Jack.
You're still the kid I met 20 years ago.
you know.
You haven't changed…
a bit.
Thank you. Elinor. Neither have you.
- [knocking on door]
- [door opens]
We're ready for you on set. Mr. Palmer.
[dramatic music playing]
She's not gonna fuck this up again.
is she?
I guarantee you.
she's going to blow you away.
- Is she ready?
- I'll check.
Hurry.
[prop master] You good with the money?
- Looks realistic.
- Yeah. What about the gun?
Well. we're still having a problem
with the firing mechanism.
¡No. carajo! It still sounds like that?
Hi there. It's Jack calling for Irving.
Jack Conrad.
One o'clock. All right. fine.
I'll call back then. Thanks.
There you are.
- We have a serious fucking problem.
- What?
- [Irv] The band looks mixed.
- What do you mean?
I mean. the other players
are a lot darker than Sid.
- So?
- [Irv] So...
- Manny. do you think I could say a line?
- No! Get back to the shot. pendejo!
In your wide. next to them.
Sidney looks white.
- [Manny] But he's Black.
- They won't think that in the South.
To them. this'll look like a mixed band.
That means we won't be able
to book the movie there.
The South is big money.
That's half the revenue lost.
No. that's not possible.
Nellie needs this movie to work.
Forget working. it's not even worth
finishing at that rate.
Wallach'll just pull the plug.
What do you suggest?
Oh. he did. did he?
Okay. then I'll call back at 4:00. Thanks.
[music ends abruptly]
- [Manny] Sidney?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- [Manny] For the lighting.
Just to match the other players.
For the lighting.
[Manny] Sí.
I know.
But look around.
Your fellow players.
if we don't get the shot.
the studio will shut the picture down
and they won't get paid.
You're an actor now. Sidney.
Actors change their appearance for roles.
It's normal.
[sighs]
It's going to be on you. Sidney.
You are risking all these guys' ability
to feed their families over makeup.
Gracias.
We all good?
- [dramatic music continues]
- Left for the day. huh?
Well. here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna come down there
and see for myself.
No. that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
Thank you.
I'm sorry. I just can't have you
in here right now.
He left for the day.
but I can take a message for you...
Thank you.
[dramatic music concludes]
[director] Cut!
That is a wrap on Sid.
[applauding]
Uh. Mr. Torres? We can't find Miss LaRoy.
Qué?
She's gone.
[man] Going over to Stage 4!
- You'll need that to come back.
- It's okay. I won't be back.
[door slams open]
Madame? Let's chat.
I'm on a deadline. darling.
You know. when I first moved to L.A..
you know what the signs
on all the doors read?
- "No actors or dogs allowed."
- [chuckles]
Yeah. I changed that.
I helped build this place you call home.
I've never had any illusions about us.
I've never pretended we're friends.
We're friendly.
I scratch yours. you scratch mine.
That's our work.
But this?
This is something else.
[sighs]
- What do you want. Jack?
- I want to know why you wrote it.
No. you want to know why they laughed.
Would you like me to tell you?
Why they laughed.
Sure. Elinor. Why?
There is no why.
It wasn't your voice.
It wasn't a conspiracy.
And it certainly wasn't anything I wrote.
There's nothing
you could have done differently.
There's nothing you can do.
Your time has run out.
There is no why. Stop questioning it.
- I'm on a dry spell.
- [Elinor] No.
It's over.
It's been over for a while. I'm sorry.
Elinor. you peddle gossip.
You don't make anything.
You don't know what it is
to put yourself out there.
You're just a cockroach.
I've been counted out before.
This isn't new to me.
Have you ever stopped to think why.
when there's a house fire.
the people die
and the cockroaches all survive?
Jesus Christ.
What happened was you thought
the house needed you.
It doesn't.
Doesn't need you any more
than it needs the roaches.
And the roaches. knowing this.
crawl back into the dark.
lay low. and make it through.
See. but you.
you held the spotlight.
It's those of us in the dark.
the ones who just watch.
who survive.
A house fire.
And there'll be hundreds more like it too.
An earthquake could
wipe this town off the map
and wouldn't make a difference.
It's the idea that sticks.
There'll be a hundred more Jack Conrads.
Hundred more mes.
Hundred more conversations
just like this one.
over and over again. until God knows when.
Because it's bigger than you.
I know it hurts.
No one asks to be left behind.
But in a hundred years.
when you and I are both long gone…
any time someone threads
a frame of yours through a sprocket.
you will be alive again.
You see what that means?
One day. every person on every film
shot this year will be dead.
And one day. all those films
will be pulled from the vaults.
and all their ghosts will dine together.
and adventure together.
go to the jungle. to war together.
A child born in 50 years
will stumble across your image
flickering on a screen
and feel he knows you. like a friend.
though you breathed your last
before he breathed his first.
You've been given a gift. Be grateful.
Your time today is through. but…
you'll spend eternity
with angels and ghosts.
[Jack] Thank you for that.
[banging on door]
[banging on door continues]
[Nellie] Manny! I need your help.
I'm in so much trouble
and I really need your help.
Calm down and tell me what happened.
[Nellie] I fucked up. Manny.
I fucked up. Manny.
And I know you've been trying to help me.
and I've just... I kept fucking up.
Now I really need your help.
and I hate to ask...
Calm down.
[speaking Spanish]
Okay. yeah. I was in Cal-Neva.
and I was playing cards and there was...
This guy. McKay. runs the place
and. he's... like. you don't fuck with...
- [Manny. in English] How much?
- He's…
[speaking Spanish]
- It's a lot. It's a lot.
- [Manny. in English] How much do you owe?
Eighty-five grand.
- They took me…
- ¿Como? How?
He took me back into a room.
Manny. and they said
if I don't have the money
by the end of the week.
they're gonna pour acid on my pussy.
[Manny speaking Spanish]
And they're not kidding.
[Manny. in English]
They will fucking kill you.
These people are killers.
- Pay them. okay?
- I can't.
You don't fuck with these kind of people.
Nellie. You just pay them.
- I can't pay them.
- [Manny] What do you mean?
I don't have the money
to pay them. I don't have...
You're Nellie LaRoy.
Of course you have the money.
No. I don't. It's...
It's gone. It's...
My dad's diner and the...
We don't own the houses.
I don't have that...
I don't have that money.
[speaking Spanish]
- [sobs]
- [shouting in Spanish]
[in English] …fucking help!
[sobs] Please be nice to me. Manny.
Please.
[shouting in Spanish]
[in English] You fucked my life!
I have nowhere else to go.
You're my only friend.
You're the only one. Manny!
You're the only one
who's ever been nice to me.
You're the only one who's ever cared.
[speaking Spanish]
[in English] I've always helped you.
and all you've done is break my heart!
[Nellie sobs] Please.
They're gonna kill me.
- [sobbing]
- [breathing heavily]
[inaudible]
[Nellie] I tried.
Manny. I did everything you said.
I tried.
[sobbing]
[sniffling]
[sighs heavily] Don't go home.
Stay here for a couple of days.
I'm gonna fix it.
[Nellie] Thank you.
[Manny] I'll fix it.
[Italian opera music playing
over phonograph]
[Italian opera continues playing]
[telephone ringing]
[telephone continues ringing]
[Irv] Jack! It's Irv.
Jack?
Listen. I've been trying you for a while.
I got some great news.
I got a job for you. It's a prestige one.
Lead got sick mid-shoot.
Quick start. quick wrap. [sighs]
Need you. Jack.
- Jack?
- Yeah.
- [Irv] You heard what I said?
- Yeah. I heard.
[Irv] Okay? So? What do you think?
Yeah. I just have one question.
It's a piece of shit. isn't it?
[Irv chuckles] What?
And I'd be bailing you out. wouldn't I?
[Irv] No. No. Of course not.
Irv. let's just call it for what it is.
That's all I ask.
I'll do your movie. I'll bail you out.
All I want in return is a little honesty.
Can you do that. Irv?
Can you be honest with me
for ten seconds or so?
I'd be bailing you out. wouldn't I?
[Irv] Yeah. you'd be bailing me out.
And it's a piece of shit. isn't it?
[Irv] Yeah. it's a piece of shit.
[chuckles]
Okay. Irv. I'll see you on set.
[telephone receiver clacks]
[seagulls squawking]
[crew member yelling] Mr. Conrad?
[indistinct chatter]
Harold. how you doing?
I'm doing good. Jack. How about you?
I'm doing okay.
How many movies have we done together now?
[Harold] This makes 82.
Huh.
- Eighty-two.
- [Harold] That's right.
[whistles]
[man] Beautiful. isn't she?
The great wide ocean.
You remember your first time at sea?
Kid. I'll never forget it.
[director] Cut! Fantastic!
Not a dry eye in the house.
- Great. For this next take…
- Yeah.
…I want to see more of
that real emotion.
Okay. You know? Really dig into it.
- Yeah.
- Find it out here.
- Find it on that horizon.
- [man] Yeah.
[director] A never-ending horizon
that has brought you
all the way to this point.
Brought you so far in life. You know?
Jack?
- You good to go again?
- Sure.
[upbeat music playing]
- Nellie?
- [Nellie] Manny!
Manny. I got it all figured out.
Because I know that you've been trying
to get my career going.
I've had an idea.
I was thinking I can dance.
If I can dance. I bet I can sing.
'Cause you can do anything
if you set your mind to it.
Nellie. you have to stop this. okay?
You really have to stop.
I'm figuring out how to get the money.
Exactly! This is how
we make the money back.
I'm gonna tell Wallach
that we're gonna finish the movie. okay?
And first. all this. all this fucking mess
that you are doing every fucking day
is part of your process.
Manny. it's gonna be like
nothing anyone's ever seen.
- It's going to be beautiful.
- [telephone rings]
- Hello?
- Manny. it's done.
I got the money and I know a guy
who will set the meet.
You got it? Okay.
but you're going to be there. right?
Don't worry. I'll be there the whole time.
See you Friday.
Nellie. we did it. okay?
Fuck Don Wallach!
Fuck all of this shit. okay?
- Fuck him. Manny! Yes!
- Fuck it! Fuck it!
Yes!
[upbeat music concludes]
- How did you get the money so fast?
- I have my ways. Don't worry.
- And it's all in here?
- Yes.
How do you know the guy?
I sold him keys a while back.
He works for McKay.
So. we give him the bag.
he calls McKay. and the threat
against Nellie is off.
Okay. okay.
I'm not used to these kind of people.
They're no worse than movie people.
You good?
Yeah. yeah. Let's go.
Remember. A monologue in the next picture.
[instrumental music playing]
- [The Count] Wilson.
- Been a while.
Good to see you. Meet Manny.
[clearing throat]
[Wilson] Nice to meet you. Manny.
And nice to meet you. sir.
I believe this belongs to you.
[Wilson] You're a producer?
A studio executive.
Jim heard you were a big producer.
He's here now.
He'd love to buy you guys a drink.
- That's very kind of him. but...
- Sounds great. Yeah.
Great. Follow me.
Gotta be polite. One drink.
Fuck.
[Wilson] Jim.
This is Manny and The Count.
How do you boys do?
I'm James McKay.
- How do you do. sir?
- Hello.
Sit down.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- [Manny] Hi.
[James] Do you want a drink?
It's brandy mixed with ether.
- Yes.
- Sure.
Wilson. will you
get us some drinks. please?
Sir. I just wanted to say how sorry I am
that things got out of hand.
Nonsense. You came through.
That's what counts.
So. you boys are friends
with Nellie LaRoy?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
Too bad what happened to her career. huh?
Such a shame. yeah. It's sad.
Her new movie will work.
So you're the movie producer.
Studio executive.
I got some movie ideas myself.
You wanna hear them?
Yes.
Please.
[clears throat]
Okay.
Hmm. [chuckles]
Okay. so…
there's a ten year old kid
and he's a prodigy
at all these adult things.
He's super smart with words.
He can play the piano and recite Lincoln
and all this stuff.
Here's the twist.
Turns out he's a 50-year-old midget.
He only looks like he's a kid.
The joke's on us.
[chuckles] That's really good. Wow.
- It's very good.
- It's great. yeah.
- Very good.
- I am sorry.
I'm gonna check on the drinks.
I don't know where Wilson went.
[Manny sighs] Stupid…
One drink and we leave.
Right after this we leave.
- Calm down.
- I am calm. cabrón.
No. you're not. You're very nervous.
I'm not here for drinks and fun. okay?
I'm in your debt.
- You're not in my debt.
- Whose money it is?
The guy makes it by the kilo.
It's not a big deal.
What guy?
You never told me how you got it.
Tony. The prop guy.
- I thought I told you that.
- It's the prop guy's money?
No. it's the money that he makes.
What do you mean? Like. his income?
No. it's his...
It's from your bank heist picture.
It's movie money.
It's prop money.
The money in the bag is prop money?
Well. where was I
gonna get 85 grand in two days?
We have to go now. pendejo cabrón!
[shushes] Calm.
[James] Have I interrupted something?
[The Count] No. no.
Oh. thank you.
I got more ideas.
You ever heard of Wyatt Earp?
He died a couple of years ago.
I met him once.
Little known fact.
the greatest hero of the Wild West
couldn't count.
- No?
- [James] No.
So I was thinking.
you make a movie about him.
and in it. you make him
full-fledged retard.
What?
You okay?
- What?
- [James] You're sweating.
It's probably the ether. It's...
Oh.
I thought you were just
excited about the idea.
[laughs]
[all laugh]
My next idea is my best.
The world's most fearless warrior.
I know just the guy to play him.
You just build the movie around him.
He is sensational.
He is?
Would you like to meet him?
Sure. I can have the studio set...
Oh. no. no. no. I'm going to see him now.
He's at the Blockhouse.
- Where is that?
- It's just over the hill.
A few minutes' drive.
Wilson and I can take you there and back.
It's the best party in town.
- It's very late and we have to go.
- Oh. no. it's worth it.
I promise you.
I mean. I appreciate it.
- but we really have to go.
- [James] Trust me.
You'll never forget it.
[The Count] What's this?
[James] It's L.A.'s last real party.
Wilson. bring that cash.
This town has gotten so repressed.
This is the only place left where
you can have any fun these days.
Welcome to the asshole of Los Angeles.
[whistling]
[sinister dance music playing]
[crowd cheering. shouting]
He's two floors down! Follow me!
[fighters grunting]
[James] This city used to know
how to have a good time.
It's just such a drag now.
They still know how
to party here. though. [chuckles]
♪ There's one pet I like to pet
And every evening we get set ♪
♪ I stroke it every chance I get
It's my girl's pussy… ♪
♪ Seldom plays and never purrs… ♪
One more floor.
- ♪ But I don't mind because it's hers… ♪
- [whip cracks]
- [man groans. whimpers]
- ♪ My girl's pussy ♪
[James] This is the kind of thing
your industry needs.
[Wilson clears throat. spits]
[James] Hollywood has just become
so stale.
- Don't you agree?
- ["Aba Daba Honeymoon" playing]
♪ Aba daba daba daba daba daba daba
Said the chimpie to the monk… ♪
[James sighs] Not this floor. either.
♪ Says the monkey to the chimp… ♪
- Wilson. isn't he on tonight?
- Thought he was.
[Manny] Sir?
- It's very late.
- [James] Oh. no. no. no. no.
I promised you a sight.
You're getting a sight.
Let's try one more floor.
♪ Means monk I love but you ♪
♪ Daba daba daba in monkey talk
Means chimp I love you too ♪
♪ Then the big baboon one night in June
He married them and very soon ♪
[James] Bear with me. fellas.
Wait till you see this guy.
- I think we can make millions together!
- [spits]
["Aba Daba Honeymoon" concludes]
- [screams]
- [The Count] Oh. shit!
[laughs]
That was so good!
Oh. come on. boys.
it's just on the other side.
It's worth it. I promise.
[growls]
[James] Okay.
Oh. yes. This is it.
Yeah.
[humming]
Yes. I think I can hear him.
Come on.
Yes.
[crowd shouting. cheering]
I'm so excited for you.
You're gonna love him!
Yes! Yes! He's the next big thing! Whoo!
Incredible. isn't he?
You either are a star
or you aren't. And he is!
Watch what he does.
It has to be seen to be believed.
[shushes]
[squeaking]
[James] Keep watching.
[crowd gasps]
[crowd cheering]
Yes!
He's just made for the movies. isn't he?
They found him in a forest in Oregon.
He will do anything for cash.
Wilson. quick. give me a 20.
More! Eat another rat!
Give me another one.
It's fake.
No.
No. come on. [chuckles]
- Let me explain...
- We were gonna make movies together.
Let me explain. Please. please.
No. no! No. no. no. no. no.
Hey. no. no! Wait. wait!
[grunts]
- [grunts]
- [pants]
What the fuck?
[crowd clamoring]
Back off! Back off!
[gunshots]
[Manny screams]
[screaming]
♪ Aba daba daba daba daba daba daba
Said the monkey to the chimp… ♪
♪ And every evening… ♪
- [crowd cheering. shouting]
- [Manny yells in Spanish]
[sinister dance music playing]
[sinister dance music concludes]
[gunshots]
Oh. shit!
- [yells in Spanish]
- [screams]
[both panting]
[soft jazz music playing]
[Lewis] You have to see Dresden.
It's the most beautiful city in Germany.
[Rebecca] Jack said
he was gonna take me to Greece.
- [Lewis] Greece?
- Isn't that right. honey?
That's right.
The architecture is amazing.
You'll love it.
- Santorini.
- [Rebecca] I hear it's so beautiful.
- Fay!
- Jack.
[speaking Italian]
[in English]
Folks. I'd like to introduce you
to the wild and wonderful Lady Fay.
This is Rebecca. This is Lewis.
- How do you do?
- [Rebecca] Hello.
- [Jack] What's your excuse?
Just wandering through?
- Mmm. Something like that.
- Let me get you a drink.
- Were you shooting?
- No.
Just wanted some air.
What's next?
- I'm going to Europe. actually.
- Are you?
Yeah. Pathé wants me.
That's great!
Pathé's got really good taste.
Thank you.
Jack's back!
Way to go. Jack!
- [Lady Fay] So how's your movie?
- It's shit.
Another giant swing at mediocrity.
Well. the girl seems nice.
She is.
And she has no idea
it'll end like all the others.
You like her?
No.
You might want to save her.
You okay. sweetie?
It was the most magical place
in the world. wasn't it?
It was.
Another set. another review.
Another romance. another breakup.
I'm tired. Fay.
It's okay.
I've been the luckiest bastard
in the world.
- I had a good run. didn't I?
- You sure did.
Yeah. I enjoyed that.
- I gotta run. sweetie.
- Yep.
It was so good to see you. Fay.
You're gonna do great things in Europe.
- You were always one of the good ones.
- Thank you.
- Ciao. my love.
- Ciao.
See you in Venice. See you in Prague.
I'm gonna go get those cigars.
Hey. you do a great job.
What's the best tip you've ever received?
Fifty dollars.
Who gave you that?
You did. Mr. Conrad.
It's on you now. kid. The future's yours.
[whistling]
- [gunshot]
- [thud]
[upbeat music playing]
[Manny] They're looking for us. Get up.
I don't feel good.
- [Manny] We are going to Mexico. Nellie.
- Mexico?
Mexico. Get dressed. We are going now.
I'm not going to Mexico. Are you crazy?
They are going to fucking kill us. okay?
I fucked up.
Go hit a piñata if you're homesick.
Nellie. get dressed
and get in the fucking car. now!
Manny. you're scaring me.
Okay. I need another hit.
Okay. I feel better.
Oh. hi. Do you have any coke?
Yeah. I've actually got...
Don't give her anything. pendejo.
Anything!
[The Count] All right. I won't!
Get everything you need. We get gas.
See you in ten minutes. cabrón.
Ten minutes.
And some pills. please?
Stop it. carajo.
- [speaking Spanish]
- Suck a dick. Señor Avocado.
[in English] We need
a fucking gas station. now.
Okay. "We need a gas station. now."
- [Manny] Yeah. we fucking need...
- [Nellie] "Blah. blah. blah. blah. blah."
[Manny] There! There.
Fuck! Puta madre!
- [Nellie] Oh! It's closed.
- [Manny] I know it's closed!
You know what we should do?
We should go dancing!
Manny! Oh. my...
We could dance up here.
[speaking Spanish]
Manny! Manny. come up here.
Manny! Come on. it's fun.
- [in English] No. it's not fun.
- Yes. it is.
- It's not fun.
- We can have fun.
- Puta madre!
- Okay.
- [speaking Spanish]
- [screams]
- [Manny screams]
- [tires screech]
Nellie?
Nellie!
Maybe they got dancing here! Come on!
[speaking Spanish]
Nellie.
Nellie!
Manny!
[in English] Nellie. we have to leave now!
[in Spanish] We're going!
- I'm staying. Manny. I'm not moving.
- [in English] No. no.
You know what happen if they find us.
Why are you doing this. carajo? Why?
[in Spanish] Tell me!
Don't you know they're going to kill us?
Wake up!
Manny. I shouldn't…
I shouldn't have asked you to help me.
[in English] Let me help. I want to help.
We can go to Mexico. Nellie.
And we can be happy.
- But we have to leave now.
- [Nellie] Manny. Manny.
It's the end of the road for me.
This is it for me.
Cállate.
[in English] It's not.
I'm at peace with that.
[speaking Spanish]
I'm not mad anymore. Manny…
- Nellie. cállate.
- You go to Mexico without me.
[in English] What the fuck
I'm gonna do without you?
I'm not going anywhere without you!
[speaking Spanish]
Manny…
Te amo.
Te amo. Nellie.
[speaking Spanish]
[Nellie] What have I done?
[sobs] I don't think I'm good for you.
I don't think I'm very good for you.
[in English] Nellie. I want to marry you.
I want to make you so happy every day.
Okay. it's my only job. From now on.
But we have to leave now.
Okay.
- I just want to be with you.
- Okay.
Okay. we'll…
We'll go to Mexico.
We'll go to the border
and we'll go down south
and we'll get married
and we'll have kids and...
It'll be you and me. okay?
Okay.
[man speaking Spanish]
Te amo. Nellie.
I love you. Manny.
Hey. you two with the camera!
Do you know who I am?
I'm Nellie LaRoy. bitches.
Holy shit. that is Nellie LaRoy.
That's Nellie fucking LaRoy. Come here.
This is my husband-to-be. Manny Torres.
Wait. Sorry?
We're gonna get married. [chuckles]
We're gonna get married?
[man] Are you really gonna be her husband?
Yes. Yeah.
Congratulations! Get a shot.
Get it. get it. get it.
[upbeat music continues]
[upbeat music concludes]
[Manny] Do you need anything?
- [Nellie] You go grab him. I'm good.
- [gentle music playing]
Te amo. Nellie.
I love you. Manny.
Ain't life grand.
[hums]
- [gentle music concludes]
- [humming continues]
[knocking on door]
- [Manny] Hey.
- [The Count] Hey.
I'm sorry. It was hard to find gas.
Yeah. well. I got everything we need.
This is my roommate. Kyle.
- Hey.
- [Manny] Hi.
Do you need anything?
I'm just gonna fill this up real quick.
- No. gracias. Let's go. no?
- Yeah.
[door bangs open]
[gunshots]
No. No. no. no. no. No. No. no.
Don't kill me. [sobs]
[speaking Spanish]
[in English] Please don't kill me.
I'm nobody. I'm nobody. [sobbing]
[speaking Spanish]
[in English] I can leave. Please. please.
[urinating]
[in English] I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
[sobbing continues]
Get the fuck out of L.A.
Disappear.
Nellie. Nellie?
Nellie?
Nellie!
Nellie! Nellie!
Oh. fuck!
[emcee] And introducing tonight.
a new addition to the Hart Café Band.
Fresh from pictures.
Mr. Sidney Palmer on the trumpet.
[audience applauding]
Hey. Sid. You want to say a few words?
Thank you. Tom.
I just would like to say to you
how happy I am to be here.
You all are such
a beautiful. lovely crowd.
So. thank you.
If I can. I'd like to play something
that I used to play
back in the days.
I hope you all enjoy it.
[melancholy music playing]
[melancholy music concludes]
[car horns honking]
[in Spanish] This is it.
What do you think?
That's where I used to work.
[in English] Passes. sir?
[in English] We're just looking.
Thank you.
Hola. Hi.
[in Spanish] I used to work here.
Sí?
A long time ago.
[in Spanish] I started here last year.
You like it?
- [in English] It's okay.
- Sí?
[in Spanish] They make anything good
these days?
[guard. in Spanish]
You don't go to the movies?
Not much anymore. I own an audio shop
in New York. Radios. that kind of thing.
- New York?
- Sí.
It's her first time in L.A.
- Oh yeah?
- Hola.
Nice talking to you.
- Cuídese mucho.
- You too.
I'm bored.
Really?
So early?
- Let's go.
- No. you stay.
I'll take her to the hotel.
We'll eat some ice cream.
[speaking Spanish]
- Muchas gracias.
- Bye. amor.
[both speaking Spanish]
[Silvia speaking Spanish]
- Adios.
- [Silvia. in English] Bye.
[car horn honking]
Fifty cents.
[Manny. in English] Thank you.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ All I do is dream of you
The whole night through ♪
♪ With the dawn I still go on
Dreaming of you ♪
♪ You're every thought. you're everything
You're every song I ever sing ♪
♪ Summer. winter. autumn. and spring ♪
♪ And were there more
Than 24 hours a day ♪
♪ They'd be spent in sweet content
Dreamin' away ♪
♪ When skies are grey. when skies are blue
Morning. noon and nighttime too ♪
♪ All I do the whole day through
Is dream of you ♪
[upbeat music concludes]
[man 1] Save it.
[man 2] Save it. Tell them to go home.
We're shutting down for a few weeks.
- [man 1] What?
- [man 2] Well. don't just stand there.
- Tell them.
- [man 1] Everybody go home
until further notice. What is this?
[man 3] Yeah. What's the matter?
[man 2] The jazz singer.
That's what's the matter. The jazz singer.
♪ Oh my darling little mammy
Down in Alabamy… ♪
[man 2] This is no joke. Cosmo.
It's a sensation.
The public is screaming for more.
- [Cosmo] More what?
- [man 2] Talking pictures.
Talking pictures.
- Aw. it's just a freak.
- Yeah. what a freak.
We should have such a freak
at this studio.
I told you talking pictures were a menace.
but no one would listen to me.
Don. we're gonna put
our best feet forward.
We're going to make The Dueling Cavalier
into a talking picture.
[dramatic music playing]
[woman vocalizing in film]
No. no. Miss Demont.
Round tones. round tones.
Now let me hear you read your line.
And I can't stand him.
Pierre. you shouldn't have come.
[man] She's gotta talk into the mic.
I can't pick it up.
[Miss Demont] I was talking.
wasn't I. Miss Dinsmore?
[Miss Dinsmore] Yes. my dear.
but please remember round tones.
[Miss Demont speaking faintly]
[gentle music playing]
[Miss Demont screams]
[audience laughing]
I love you. I love you.
[man] Good night. See you tomorrow.
[woman] Good night. darling.
Take care of that throat.
You're a big singing star now. remember?
This California dew is
just a little heavier than usual tonight.
[man] Really? Where I stand.
the sun is shining all over the place.
["Singin' in the Rain" playing]
♪ I'm singin' in the rain ♪
♪ Just singin' in the rain ♪
♪ What a glorious feeling ♪
♪ I'm happy again ♪
♪ I'm laughing at clouds ♪
♪ So dark up above ♪
♪ The sun's in my heart ♪
♪ And I'm ready for love ♪
♪ Let the stormy clouds chase ♪
♪ Everyone from the place ♪
♪ Come on with the rain ♪
♪ I've a smile on my face ♪
♪ I'll walk down the lane ♪
♪ With a happy refrain ♪
♪ Just singin'. singin' in the rain ♪
♪ Dancin' in the rain ♪
♪ I'm happy again ♪
["Singin' in the Rain" fades]
[upbeat music playing]
[Nellie] Tell me why.
- [Manny] Why?
- [Nellie] Yeah. tell me why.
[Manny] I don't know why.
I just want to be part
of something bigger.
To be part of something important.
something that lasts.
that means something.
[upbeat music intensifies]
[upbeat music continues]
[music intensifies]
[upbeat music ends abruptly]
[musical flourish]
[upbeat music concludes]
[upbeat jazz music playing]
[upbeat jazz music concludes]
[jazzy music playing]
[jazz music concludes]
[gentle music playing]
[gentle music concludes]
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-